Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Ken Nash Collection - Audio Cassettes, 1986-1999
  - Subseries VIII:F: Other Events Audio Cassettes, 1987-1997.
    - AFL-CIO Officers Election Forum (tape 1 of 2), May 22, 1996; cuid6099 (Box 67, Cassette 215, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_215)
    - AFL-CIO Officers Election Forum (tape 2 of 2), May 22, 1996; cuid6100 (Box 67, Cassette 216, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_216)
    - AFL-CIO "Union Summer" Press Conference, May 1, 1996; cuid6101 (Box 67, Cassette 217, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_217)
    - Clinton, Bill Health Care Plan Press Conference, Undated; cuid6102 (Box 68, Cassette 218)
    - Collective Bargaining Meeting, Jan 5, 1987; cuid6103 (Box 68, Cassette 219)
    - Contract Agreement Press Conference, Oct 24, 1994; cuid6104 (Box 68, Cassette 220)
    - Contract Agreement Press Conference, City Hall, Undated; cuid6105 (Box 68, Cassette 221)
    - Cornell University Labor Scholars Panel Discussion, Undated; cuid6106 (Box 68, Cassette 222)
    - DC 37 Fashion Show, Undated; cuid6107 (Box 68, Cassette 223)
    - DC 37 General Session (tape 1 of 3), Jul 13, 1987; cuid6108 (Box 68, Cassette 224)
    - DC 37 General Session (tape 2 of 3), Jul 13, 1987; cuid6109 (Box 68, Cassette 225)
    - DC 37 General Session (tape 3 of 3), Jul 13, 1987; cuid6110 (Box 68, Cassette 226)
    - DC 37 Hispanic Heritage Month Celebration (tape 1 of 2), Undated; cuid6111 (Box 68, Cassette 227)
    - DC 37 Hispanic Heritage Month Celebration (tape 2 of 2), Undated; cuid6112 (Box 68, Cassette 228)
    - DC 37 Nominating Meeting, Jan 27, 1987; cuid6113 (Box 68, Cassette 229)
    - DC 37 Unidentified Event [DAT Cassette], Undated; cuid6114 (Box 68, Cassette 230)
    - DC 37 Women's Committee Awards Dinner (tape 1 of 2), Mar 20, 1997; cuid6115 (Box 68, Cassette 231)
    - DC 37 Women's Committee Awards Dinner, Mar 20, 1997; cuid6116 (Box 68, Cassette 232)
    - Financial Crisis Panel Discussion, Nov 26, 1991; cuid6117 (Box 68, Cassette 233)
    - Gay Pride Authors [Blank?], Jul 9, 1996; cuid6118 (Box 68, Cassette 234)
    - International Change, Globalization, and the European Union Forum, Feb 10, 1996; cuid6119 (Box 68, Cassette 235)
    - Labor and the Community Forum, Mar 31, [?]; cuid6120 (Box 68, Cassette 236)
    - Labor and the Community Forum [DAT Cassette], Mar 31, [?]; cuid6121 (Box 68, Cassette 237)
    - Local 420 Rally at First Baptist Church, Dec 18, 1996; cuid6122 (Box 68, Cassette 238)
    - McEntee, Gerald W., undated; cuid6123 (Box 68, Cassette 248)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 1 of 3), Mar 1, 1994; cuid6124 (Box 68, Cassette 239)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 2 of 3), Mar 1, 1994; cuid6125 (Box 68, Cassette 240)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 3 of 3), Mar 1, 1994; cuid6126 (Box 68, Cassette 241)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 1 of 2) [beginning inaudible], Jan 18, 1995; cuid6127 (Box 68, Cassette 242)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 2 of 2), Jan 18, 1995; cuid6128 (Box 68, Cassette 243)
    - Rifkin, Bernie Dedication, Dec 11, 1995; cuid6129 (Box 68, Cassette 244)
    - Social Security Advisory Committee Report Press Conference, Jan 6, 1997; cuid6130 (Box 68, Cassette 245)
    - Tuberculosis Panel Discussion, Undated; cuid6131 (Box 68, Cassette 246)
    - Unidentified Event, Undated; cuid6132 (Box 68, Cassette 247)
- Series IX: Ken Nash Collection - 2015 Donation, 1993-2014; 2015.062
  - District Council 37 Radio Broadcasts, 1993-2003; 1998-2003; cuid6133 (Box 70, Box 73, Box 74, Box 75, Box Shared Tamiment 139, Box Shared Tamiment 147, Box Shared Tamiment 085)
  - Award Dinner and Banquet Programs, 2012, 2014; cuid6134 (Box 71)
  - 65th Anniversary Commemorative History Book, 2009; cuid6135 (Box 71)
  - Labor Magazines, 2014; cuid6136 (Box 71)
- Series X: Audio Reels - Other, 1965
  - 40 Audio Reels (appear to be radio spots--some are in Spanish), 1965, undated; cuid6137 (Box 69)
- Series XI: Archived Websites, September 2007-ongoing; cuid6138; 5 websites in 5 archived websites.
  District Council 37 (DC 37) is a local union of the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) which represents New York City public employees and employees in the healthcare industry. DC 37 was founded in 1944. The website contains information on locals, contracts and agreements, news listings, press releases, their newsletter, Public Employee Press, their political action campaign and PEOPLE (Public Employees Organized to Promote Legislative Equality) political program, lobbying institute, the blog, La Voz Latinoamericana Radio Show, DC 37 Radio Show, DC 37 TV Show, white papes, and member benefits and services. Capture of the website began in 2007. In 2008, the union focused on legislation to remove the residency requirement for DC 37 members; the World Trade Center Disability Law allowing DC 37 members who worked on 9/11 rescue and/or recovery to apply for disability benefits; stop lay-offs in the off-track betting sector; and contract negotiations. In 2009, the website redesigned and focused on Department of Education lay-offs, New York State health care funding, the H1N1 virus, disaster relief, the Unified Call Taking System for first responders, and Library cutbacks. During bargaining campaigns and threatened New York City budget cuts and layoffs, the union often held rallies and protests. In 2012, the website focused on privatization of New York City parking, public employee pensions, Hurricane Sandy, and a congressional briefing on paying private contractors with public funds to deliver federally funded services. The mayoral campaign was featured on the website in 2013. In 2014, their 2010-2017 contract was ratified. In 2015, Executive Director Lillian Roberts retired, they started a student debt program, and called for a CUNY contract. In 2017, they began bargaining for a new contract. In 2018, the website redesigned and featured the We Never Quit campaign. In 2020-2022, contained a significant amount of material related to the union's response to the COVID-19 pandemic and the 2021 mayoral campaign. Other programs featured on the website overtime include the Education Fund courses, committee updates, Municipal Employees Legal Services (MELS), the Labor, Faith and Community Outreach program, the Lillian Roberts Women's Leadership Academy, health and hospitals productivity program, quality of work life program, and services for laid-off members.
  Also includes the website created by DC 37 to update members on information related to the COVID-19 pandemic. The website contains worksite updates and reopening plans, resources for members, government benefits, and related news. During the COVID-19 pandemic, the radio and tv shows were paused.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued semiannually.
  In 2020, https://www.dc37.net/ and https://dc37blog.net/ began to be captured monthly.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of http://www.dc37.net/, https://dc37blog.net/, https://www.dc37covid19.net/, and http://www.dc37pep.net/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
- Series XII: Films and videos, 1972-1999
  - Dignity of Work Series (Films, Inc.), "Clerical Workers", 1972-10-10; cuid6139 (Film wag.265_cuid6139, Box Digitized Access Files, File wag.265_cuid6139)
  - Dignity of Work Series (Films, Inc.), "Marketing Inspector", 1972-10-06; cuid6140 (Film wag.265_cuid6140, Box Digitized Access Files, File wag.265_cuid6140)
  - Dignity of Work Series (Films, Inc.), "Zoo Keeper", 1972-12-06; cuid6141 (Film wag.265_cuid6141, Box Digitized Access Files, File wag.265_cuid6141)
  - Videos: "Keep the Doors Open," "In the Name of Corporate Greed," "Postal Workers Fight Privatization", 1998-1999; cuid6142 (Box Shared Tamiment 012)
  - Video: "Jason Turner," Up Close New York One, 1998-07-23; cuid6143 (Box Shared Tamiment 013)
  - Video: "America's Victory: The 1997 UPS Strike", undated; cuid6144 (Box Shared Tamiment 013)
  - Video: 1. Joe DeCanio, L. 376, 2. 60 Minutes-Mark Rosenthal, L. 983, undated; cuid6145 (Box Shared Tamiment 013)
  - Unprocessed Videos (Box 72)